https://www.shophq.com/p/help/shophq/privacy/?icid=gft-_-privacy

Skip to main content
{"BannerType":"default","LinkUrl":"https://www.shophq.com/a/boutique/gold-gift-wonderland?icid=GH-_-J-_-GGW-_-121120","ImageUrl":"https://www.shophq.com/images/store1/Creative2020_J/Com/Homepage/GH/121020_GH-6.png","WidthRatio":15.692307692307692,"Headline":"","Copy":"","TextColor":"","BackgoundColor":"#350000","BackgoundColorFrom":"","BackgoundColorTo":"","BackgoundImageUrl":"","BackgroundWidthRatio":-1,"Description":"Gold Gift Wonderland Event The LAST Gold Event of The Year - Up To 40% Off - Ends Sunday"}
Welcome, Guest
Sign In
Main Menu
Home
Wishlist
Track Order
Shop
Jewelry
Albany Irvin Collections
Artisan Jewelry by Samuel B.
Dallas Prince
Diamond Treasures
EFFY
Galerie de Bijoux
Gem Treasures
Gems en Vogue
Hall of Style
Kwan Collections
Heather’s Closet
Indigo Thread Co.
Journee Collection
J.W. Hulme
Kate & Mallory
Madi Claire
Manitobah Mukluks
MAYAMAR
More Brands
Elan
TVs 60" & Over
TVs 40-59"
TVs 39" & Under
Shop All TVs
TV Mounts & Accessories
Gaming
Laptops
Tablets
Networking
Blu-ray, DVD & Video
Gem Treasures
Indigo Thread Co.
Invicta
Kate & Mallory
One World
OSO Casuals
Mod X
Victoria Wieck
Waterford
Shop All Clearance
Albany Irvin Collections
Artisan Jewelry by Samuel B.
Dallas Prince
Diamond Treasures
EFFY
Galerie de Bijoux
Gem Treasures
Gems en Vogue
Hall of Style
Kwan Collections
Heather’s Closet
Indigo Thread Co.
Journee Collection
J.W. Hulme
Kate & Mallory
Madi Claire
Manitobah Mukluks
MAYAMAR
More Brands
Elan
TVs 60" & Over
TVs 40-59"
TVs 39" & Under
Shop All TVs
TV Mounts & Accessories
Gaming
Laptops
Tablets
Networking
Blu-ray, DVD & Video
Gem Treasures
Indigo Thread Co.
Invicta
Kate & Mallory
One World
OSO Casuals
Mod X
Victoria Wieck
Waterford
Shop All Clearance
Almost Gone
Help
ShopHQ Privacy Policy
Effective November 8, 2018
Scope of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how ShopHQ. (“ShopHQ”) uses, shares and protects the personal information we collect through ShopHQ’s websites (“Websites”), including ShopHQ.com ("ShopHQ.com") and affiliated websites containing links to this Privacy Policy, ShopHQ’s telephone ordering and interactive voice response services (“Telephone Services”) and ShopHQ’s mobile and other applications (“Applications”) (hereinafter, the Websites, Telephone Services, and Applications are referred to collectively as the “ShopHQ Systems”). This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into the ShopHQ Terms of Use.
Your Consent to This Privacy Policy
By browsing or using the ShopHQ Systems, you are agreeing to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the ShopHQ Systems.
This Privacy Policy May Change
We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version on ShopHQ.com. Your use of the ShopHQ Systems following any such change constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you through the ShopHQ Systems after the revised Privacy Policy is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.
The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You may access the current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked "Privacy" at the bottom of each page on ShopHQ.com and other locations in the ShopHQ Systems.
Questions Concerning Our Online Privacy Practices
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please email us at customercare@shophq.com or write to us at ShopHQ, Legal Department, 6740 Shady Oak Road, Eden Prairie, Minnesota 55344.
Privacy Notices
This Privacy Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by "privacy notices" posted on the ShopHQ Systems. For example, certain pages of ShopHQ’s Websites may contain privacy notices providing details about the ways we use or share the personal information we collect on those pages.
What Information Does ShopHQ Collect?
Information You Give Us
We collect the personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use the ShopHQ Systems – for example, the information you provide when you register, create an account, sign-in, search, apply for credit, participate in a contest or questionnaire, submit reviews, sign up for our e-mails, communicate with customer service, or purchase products, services and other retail offerings (“Merchandise”). Depending on how you use the ShopHQ Systems, you may supply us with information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, credit card information, or information about people to whom purchases will be shipped (for example, a gift recipient).
Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser
We collect information that is sent to us by your web browser, including but not limited to your IP address or device identifier, the address of the web page you were visiting when you accessed the ShopHQ Websites or Applications, the date and time of your visit, your location, and information about your computer's operating system or mobile device. Please check your browser or mobile device if you want to learn what information your browser or mobile device sends or how to change your settings. We use this information in part to create statistics that help us improve the ShopHQ Websites and Applications and make them more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. If you have created a user identity on one of your visits to the ShopHQ Websites or Applications or if you access the ShopHQ Websites or Applications by clicking on a link in an email we have sent you, we may combine the information provided by your browser with other information that identifies you personally.
Information We Collect Using Cookies and Other Web Technologies
We use "cookies" and other web technologies to collect information and support certain features of the ShopHQ Websites or Applications. For example, we use these technologies to collect information about the ways visitors use the ShopHQ Websites or Applications —which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. Cookies and other web technologies are also used to support the features and functionality of the ShopHQ Websites or Applications, for example, to track the contents of your shopping cart as you move from page to page. These technologies also permit us to keep a record of your previous choices and preferences so that we can personalize your shopping experience and save you the inconvenience of reentering information already in our database. Generally, the information we collect using these web technologies does not identify you personally; however, it may be linked to information that does identify you personally, such as the information you provide when you make a purchase or register to use a special feature of the ShopHQ Websites or Applications.
If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete our cookies as soon as you leave the ShopHQ Websites or Applications.
Although you are not required to accept our cookies when you visit the ShopHQ Websites or Applications, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of the ShopHQ Websites or Applications.
For example, and without limitation, from time to time we may collect your email address via cookies and web beacons (also known as “pixel tags”) on the ShopHQ Websites through the use of third party partners. These partners may combine your email information with other information they have access to, including mailing addresses, so that ShopHQ may serve relevant marketing offers to you via direct mail.
Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, there are not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals and, therefore, the ShopHQ Websites and Applications do not recognize DNT.
Information We Collect From Other Sources
We may supplement the information collected through the ShopHQ Systems with information we collect in other ways.
We may also supplement the information collected through the ShopHQ Systems with information from third parties, including data brokers. By supplementing your profile with information from other sources, we are better able to provide Merchandise recommendations and special offers that may be of genuine interest to you. We may also use this additional information to further personalize the ShopHQ Systems and improve your shopping experience.
Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies by Our Advertising Agents
ShopHQ uses third-party advertising companies to place online advertisements on our behalf at websites other than ShopHQ.com or ShopHQ’s other Websites. These advertising companies may use cookies and web beacons or pixel tags to target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. For example, our advertising companies may place web beacons on their clients' websites. When you visit these websites, the web beacon "tags" your computer with a "cookie" that collects and stores information about your visit to their clients’ websites. Our advertising companies use the information they collect about your use of their clients' websites to customize the advertisements you see when you visit their clients' websites, called interest-based advertising. Our advertising companies' use of cookies and web beacons is covered by their privacy policies, not by this Privacy Policy.
You have choices with respect to online advertising and can tell us and/or our partners not to collect and use this information. Note that if you choose to opt out, you may continue to see ads on ShopHQ.com and other websites, but they will not be based on how you browse and shop. To opt out of receiving interest-based advertising from third-parties, visit the following websites:
http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/
http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/
As noted above, you can also prevent some automatic collection of information by disabling cookies on your web browser.
For more information, see “Information We Collect Using Cookies and Other Web Technologies”, above.
How is Information Used and Shared?
Use of Personal Information Collected through the ShopHQ Systems We may use the personal information we collect through the ShopHQ Systems for reasons including:
to fulfill your order for ShopHQ Merchandise;
to provide you with the information or Merchandise you request or purchase;
for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
to register your purchase with the manufacturer or service provider;
to provide you with effective customer service;
to provide you with a personalized shopping experience;
to display personalized advertising when you visit the ShopHQ Websites or Applications or third-party websites;
to contact you with commercial and promotional messages, including but not limited to special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you;
to contact you with information and notices related to your use of the ShopHQ Systems or your purchases;
to invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us;
to better understand your needs and interests;
to improve the content, functionality and usability of the ShopHQ Systems;
to improve our Merchandise offerings;
to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; and
for any other purposes we identify in a specific privacy notice or other communication to you.
Our Corporate Affiliates
We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries and parent and sister corporations (our "corporate affiliates"), who may use this information to contact you with information and offers they believe will be of interest to you. The corporate affiliates' use of your personal information shall be subject to this Privacy Policy.
Our Service Providers
We may share your personal information with companies that perform services on our behalf. Our service providers are required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them and to use it only to provide services on our behalf.
ShopHQ-Branded Credit Card Information
If you participate in the ShopHQ-Branded Credit Card program, the personal information we collect in connection with your participation in that program, including the information you provide when you apply for an ShopHQ-Branded Credit Card, is shared with the financial institution or other issuer that partners with us to provide the ShopHQ-Branded Credit Card program (“Issuer”). Issuer’s use of this personal information is governed by Issuer’s own privacy policy and any contracts between you and Issuer.
Other Business Partners and Selected Vendors.
We work closely with certain business partners (including but not limited to Issuer, defined above)
and carefully selected vendors to provide you with access to their Merchandise and other offerings. We may share personally identifiable information about you with these business partners or selected vendors, and they may use this information to offer you Merchandise that they believe will be of interest to you or to address any questions or concerns that you may have about their Merchandise.
For example, if you do not have an ShopHQ-Branded Credit Card, we may share personally identifiable information about you with Issuer (defined above),
who may use this information to offer you products and services that it believes will be of interest to you.
Extended Warranty Providers and Other Vendors
If you purchase an extended warranty in connection with Merchandise you purchase through ShopHQ, we will share with the company that provides the extended warranty the information it needs to service the extended warranty and offer you renewal and other options.
Business Transfers
Information submitted to ShopHQ or the ShopHQ Systems will become part of our normal business records. Your personal information may be transferred to another company (either a corporate affiliate or an unrelated third party) that has acquired substantially all the stock or assets of ShopHQ, one of our corporate affiliates, or one of our operating divisions, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or liquidation.
Government and Legal Disclosures
We may disclose the personal information we collect through the ShopHQ Systems when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce the Terms of Use or other agreements that govern your use of the ShopHQ Systems; to protect the rights, property or safety of ShopHQ, our users or others; or to protect your vital interests. If you have purchased Merchandise from us on extended payment terms, it may be necessary for us to file certain information about you with state or local government offices to protect our security interest in that Merchandise or to provide certain information about you to collection agencies in the event of non-payment or a payment dispute.
What Choices Do You Have?
ShopHQ respects your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. We generally ask you to indicate your choices at the time that you register as a user of ShopHQ.com or another location on the ShopHQ Systems where you provide your personal information. When you register as a user of the ShopHQ Systems, you automatically start to receive information, including commercial and promotional messages, periodically via e-mail. You may "opt-out" of receiving our commercial and promotional emails at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the particular email. You may also manage your subscription and email preferences by clicking on "My Account" on ShopHQ.com, ShopHQ’s Applications or by sending us an email. To send us an email, please email us at customercare@shophq.com.
For more information on your choices concerning online tracking and online advertising, see the “Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies by Our Advertising Agents” above.
How Can You Update or Correct Your Personal Information?
You may update your account settings information, including your name, contact information, credit card information, shipping and billing addresses, and subscription and email preferences at any time by clicking on "My Account" at ShopHQ.com. Instructions for updating your information are provided under "Account Settings." You can change your account settings at any time and as often as necessary. When you update your account settings, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records. You are responsible for ensuring that we have up-to-date and active contact information for you on file, including email address and any telephone number.
Minors who post comments or other information to the ShopHQ Websites or Applications so that it is visible to others are able to request that the information be removed by contacting us by email at customercare@shophq.com or writing to us at ShopHQ, Legal Department, 6740 Shady Oak Road, Eden Prairie, Minnesota 55344. Note that although we can help make sure the information is no longer visible on the ShopHQ Websites or Applications, this does not ensure complete or comprehensive deletion of your information from ShopHQ’s internal systems and/or other websites and services beyond our control.
Special Notice to California Residents
We may share some of your information with third-party companies with whom we have contracts to provide Merchandise and/or with companies that use the information for their marketing purposes. California law permits you to request, once per calendar year, information regarding the disclosure of your personal information (specifically, categories of information and the identity of the third parties) during the previous calendar year to any third party for its own direct marketing purposes. To make this request, please contact us as explained above.
Security
ShopHQ has implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure with industry standard measures in place to protect the security of the personal information we collect through the ShopHQ Systems. For example, we use Transport Layer Security (“TLS”) to encrypt your credit card information as it travels over the Internet, and no credit card information is stored in ShopHQ’s infrastructure. It is important that you understand, however, that no website or database is completely secure or "hacker proof." You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse, for example, by protecting your passwords. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to the ShopHQ Systems. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the ShopHQ Systems.
Links to Other Web Sites
ShopHQ’s Websites may contain links to other websites operated by ShopHQ and its corporate affiliates and service partners. They also may contain links to websites that are owned and operated by unrelated third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected through the ShopHQ Systems. It does not apply to personal information collected on any website that does not contain a link to this Privacy Policy, nor to any website operated by any third party. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy. We recommend you review the privacy policy posted on any website you visit before using the website or providing any personal information about yourself.
Children and Minors
The ShopHQ Systems are not directed at nor targeted to children under the age of 13. We do not use the ShopHQ Systems to knowingly solicit personal information from or market to children under age 13 absent verifiable parental consent. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not submit any personal information to us.
If you become aware of any personally identifiable information we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us as described above under “Questions Concerning Our Online Privacy Practices.”
Back to Top
Contact Us
800-884-2212 - Sales
800-676-5523 - Service
FAQs
Live Chat
Connect with Us
Our Hosts
iMedia Brands
ShopHQ | Bulldog Shopping | ShopHQ Health | LaVenta | Float Left | Our Galleria | i3PL
Terms of Use | Privacy | Accessibility | Close Caption
©2020 ShopHQ. All rights reserved. All trademarks, service marks and logos are owned by or registered to ShopHQ. All other product or brand names are trademarks of their respective owners.
Site Map
Order By Phone
Customer Service
TOP
